ttgasia.com 2019-05-31

# Privacy Policy | TTG Asia

**Privacy Policy**

_Last updated August 2, 2018_

We are committed to protecting your privacy and personal information.

**ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

In order to run our business and to provide you with our products and services, we require certain personal information (your “personal information”) that includes information that identifies you and, with regard to the need to meet certain legal requirements, the location from which you send us your personal information. We will take commercially reasonable measures to protect the privacy and security of your information, but if you do not agree with this Privacy Policy or the additional descriptions of how we process your personal information (how we use, share, disclose, store and delete it), you should not use our Services. If you register for an event and we seek to share your personal information with the event sponsor and/or other third parties we will, depending on your jurisdiction, request your affirmative consent to do so on the registration form.

**PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT OR RECEIVE**

In the course of providing our products and services, and as required for us to provide our products and services to you, we receive, collect store and use your personal information, as described below. This information may include your name, address, telephone number, email address and the IP address of the device you used to contact us. The ways in which we obtain your information may include:

a) Your orders for products, subscriptions or services.

b) Your inquiries sent to our offices or our website.

c) Your registration for an event, including events, conferences and meetings.

d) Data obtained through use of “cookies” and other related analytics and technologies

e) Apps or other software created or developed for use in connection with our products and services.

If you sign up for an event for which registration is open to the public, your name, company name and other identifying information may be viewed by others.

The legal bases for our uses, sharing and disclosures (“processing”) of your personal information include, as pertinent, where:

a) Necessary to perform the contractual obligations in agreements with you to provide products or services;

b) You have consented to the processing as set out in this Policy, which consent you can revoke at any time;

c) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation, a court order or to exercise or defend a legal claim;

d) Necessary for the purposes of our or a third-party’s legitimate business interests (so long as those interests do not override personal rights as indicated by law);

e) You have expressly made your personal information public; and

f) Necessary to protect your vital interests or other of others.

**FINANCIAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT OR RECEIVE**

If you choose to purchase services, products or subscriptions we may collect credit card information, bank account information and information necessary to verify your identity, such as date of birth. In certain countries, national identifier numbers (similar to Passport Numbers) may also be collected or received if needed to verify your identity. We use commercially reasonable standards to protect this information.

**USES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION BY TTG FOR TTG’S BUSINESS PURPOSES**

If you elect to provide us personal information, we may use it as needed to deliver products and/or services to you. TTG may use personal information in a variety of ways to meet our obligations to you to provide you with a variety of services and products. These uses are based in our legitimate business interests in providing products and services to you and/or fulfilment of our contractual obligation to deliver products and services you have requested.  We have balanced these business needs carefully with your privacy rights and these uses do not improperly infringe on your privacy and confidentiality rights.  These business uses for your personal information include the following:

a) TTG may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies in order to better deliver products and services that may be of interest and benefit to you.

b) We may use your personal information for security, including analysis of the personal information to pursue our legitimate business interest in protecting our customers and website visitors against malware, cyber-attack and other crime and security risks.

c) TTG may use personal information to contact users regarding renewal of subscriptions to TTG services and products and to send product announcements or special edition e-newsletters to online registrants.

d) TTG may use personal information to send notification of TTG’s or our partners’ products and services by such methods as email and/or postal mail.

e) We may aggregate and anonymize personal information provided under this Privacy Policy to create anonymized data sets which will then be used to improve our and our affiliates’ products and services. We may also share aggregated anonymized personal information with clients, customers, prospective clients and customers or business partners in order to demonstrate usage of the services, or to identify industry and advertising trends.

f) If you provide financial information, we use that information primarily to verify your credit card information and collect payments for your purchases, orders, subscriptions, etc.

g) If you participate in a TTG educational programme, event, or other time-sensitive programs, we use personal information to contact you to remind you of upcoming deadlines or additional information concerning these programs.

h) TTG occasionally conducts subscriber and/or user surveys to better target our content to our audiences. The aggregated information collected is anonymized (identifying information removed) and sometimes shared with our advertisers, however, we do not share specific individual information with third parties.

i) TTG operates several websites featuring its travel-related content and services. TTG may share personal information collected from users of its websites internally across these websites to better serve its users by permitting us to reference services across our spectrum of offerings and point you toward the best products and services for your needs.

j) We may share personal information where we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, a court order, or legal process served on TTG, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

k) We may share such information where we have a good faith belief that it is necessary in order to investigate (or assist in the investigation of), prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, cyber attack, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of TTG’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

l) If TTG is acquired by or merged with another company, we will transfer information about you to this other company in connection with the acquisition or merger.

m) TTG has numerous products and services and therefore numerous email and promotion lists. In an effort to allow users to tailor their participation in TTG services and promotions, TTG provides users the ability to choose specific lists or products of interest and opt-out options are product and use/list specific. All email promotions sent from TTG provide an opt-out link at the bottom of the email pursuant to which users can opt-out of specific products and promotions. If you receive one of these emails and wish to object to this processing of your information or unsubscribe please follow the instructions given in each email or contact [_DPO_ _@ttg_ _asia_ _.com_](mailto:DPO@ttgasia.com)

From time to time we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our Privacy Policy. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our website.

Right to object. You may object to TTG using your personal information for the above purposes at any time by contact [_DPO_ _@ttg_ _asia_ _.com_](mailto:DPO@ttgasia.com) If you do so, TTG will cease using your personal information for the above purposes (i.e., under a legitimate interest set out above) and remove it from its systems unless such personal information is permitted to be used by TTG for another purpose set out in this Privacy Policy or TTG determines and demonstrates a compelling legitimate interest to continue in processing your personal information.

**SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES**

In general, TTG does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you have requested, when we have your consent as indicated in Section I of this Policy, as follows:

a) TTG may use personal information collected through its website to send out targeted email promotions on behalf of its advertisers and industry partners.

b) We may provide personal information about our users to trusted partners and vendors who work on behalf of or with TTG under written confidentiality and similar agreements prohibiting such parties’ further use of the information. These companies may use your personal information to help TTG communicate with you about offers from TTG and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to use or share this information.

c) When you register for an educational program, contest, event, or other promotion that is sponsored by a third party we will, depending upon your jurisdiction, seek your affirmative consent to provide the third party personal information, in a manner clearly specified on the registration materials, unless otherwise posted in connection with the promotion.

d) TTG may from time to time share limited personal information such as email addresses, company name, job title and state of business or residence with trusted third parties who deliver content that is likely to be of interest to you.

**COOKIES**

With your consent, the personal information that TTG may collect using cookies or other automated methods may include, for example, your IP address, cookie information, a unique device or user ID, browser type, system type, the content and pages that you access on the TTG websites, the frequency and duration of your visits to our website, the page from which you navigated to the Website. TTG may also use cookies to store session validators on your hard drive.  On our website, TTG may use this passively collected data to:

a) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during you visit or the next time you visit our website.

b) monitor your participation in various sections of our website.

c) customize services to you.

d) monitor website usage metrics such as total visitors and pages viewed

e) administer, operate and improve our website and our other products and services, including those tailored to you.

**CHOICE AND CONTROL  **

You may withdraw your consent or otherwise object to uses of your information as described above by contacting [_DPO_ _@ttg_ _asia_ _.com_](mailto:DPO@ttgasia.com). You may also withdraw your consent to email marketing by unsubscribing, using the unsubscribe link in such communications. If you do so, TTG will cease using your personal information for the above purposes and remove it from its systems unless such personal information is permitted to be used by TTG for another purpose set out in this Privacy Policy or TTG determines and demonstrates a compelling legitimate interest to continue in processing your personal information In case of withdrawal of consent, TTG will not process your personal information subject to this consent any longer unless legally required to do so. In case TTG is required to retain your personal information for legal reasons your personal information will be restricted from further processing and only retained for the term required by law. However, any withdrawal has no effect on past processing of personal information by TTG up to the point in time of your withdrawal. Furthermore, if your use of a TTG offering requires your prior consent, TTG will not be (any longer) able to provide the relevant product, service, offer, or event to you after your withdrawal. Please direct any such request for withdrawal to, or write to TTG at [_DPO_ _@ttg_ _asia_ _.com_](mailto:DPO@ttgasia.com)

You can request from TTG, at any time, the correction or deletion of such personal information. To make such a request, please contact the email set forth below and specify in detail the information or the activity to which your request relates. Furthermore, you may contact TTG if you believe that the personal information that TTG has is incorrect.

Depending upon your location, you may benefit from a number of rights with regard to your personal information that we process. These rights are defined and, in some cases limited, by the laws of your jurisdiction. These rights include (a) data portability, including the right to obtain a copy of the personal information you have provided to TTG; (b) data correction (also known as rectification, including the ability to request correction or amendment of your personal information and (c) data deletion, including the right to have TTG delete your personal information except for information that we are required to retain.

You may inquire about the exercise of these rights and, if the laws of your jurisdiction permit, exercise them as permitted by law by contacting [ _DPO_ _@ttg_ _asia_ _.com_](mailto:DPO@ttgasia.com)

**SECURITY**

The security of your personal information is very important to us. We utilize commercially reasonable information security standards to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. TTG supports online security using appropriately secure technology because we want your data to be safe. We bind our employees and data processors to written agreements to observe your privacy and confidentiality rights. Unfortunately, no method of internet transmission is one hundred percent secure. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its security.

**DURATION AND RETENTION**

TTG will retain your personal information only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Policy, or as required or permitted by law, and then will delete it as required by law. For example, TTG will retain your information as long as required to comply with applicable tax/revenue laws, cybersecurity and privacy laws, laws and regulations that affect the conduct of our business; to resolve disputes, enforce our agreements, cooperate with law enforcement requests or to meet other legal obligations. We may also retain log files for internal analysis purposes, though we would retain them for only a brief period except in cases where we are legally required to retain them for longer periods, and in cases where they are used for site safety and security or to improve website functionality.

**INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS**

TTG operates on a global basis. By using our products and services you understand and agree that your personal information may be transferred from the European Economic Area (EEA, which comprises the European Union countries plus Norway, Iceland, Liechtenstein) to a country which does not have an equivalent level of data protection. When your personal information is transferred from your home country to another country, the laws and regulations that protect your personal information may be different than those in your home country.

**UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. If we do, we will change the “effective date” at the top of the Privacy Policy. Before making any update that would make this Privacy Policy materially less restrictive in our use or disclosure of personal information collected prior to the update, we will provide prior notice of the update by posting notice on our Website at the top of the then-current Privacy Policy within a reasonable time before the effective date of the update. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about our collection, use, and disclosure of personal information.
